decolore.net 2019-04-14

# Privacy Policy | Decolore.Net

In the process of registering & availing various services of DeColore.net, you may need to provide personal information like you may be required to give your name, residence address, workplace address, email address, contact no, date of birth, educational qualifications and similar Personal Information.  The Personal Information is used for the purposes such as customization of the content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain services, and to contact you about our services.

We are committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of all Personal Information that you may share as a user in good faith.

Personal Information will be kept confidential and will be used for our research, marketing, and strategic client analysis objectives and other internal business purposes only. Your Personal Information shall be shared with our subscribers/advertisers and you shall be deemed to have given consent to the same. Further, the subscribers / advertisers who are listed with us, may call you, based on the query or enquiry that you make with us, enquiring about any product or services.

**Disclosure**

  * The users’ privacy is very important to us. We do not either sell or rent users’ personal information to third parties without users’ at any point.
  * We may be required from time to time to disclose users’ personal information to Governmental or law enforcing agencies or our regulators, but we will only do so under proper authority.
  * DesignAzure.com also reserves the right to make use of the personal information in any investigation or judicial process relating to fraudulent activity.

**User Responsibility:** You may use personal information gathered from DeColore.net only to follow up with another user related to a specific posting, do not to send spam or collect personal information from other user without consent.

**Modification Of Information:** You can see, modify or erase your personal information on the my account status page.

**Confidentiality of Information:** DeColore.net users agree and accept that they have been fully informed the use of features may lead to publication, to all users of DeColore.net. Users further agree that the authenticity of, and consequences from the posting by users of any personal information of themselves or any other person, are the sole responsibility of the user. Users further agree and accept that the terms of the Privacy Policy will be applicable to the use of all features, existing and new. However, the Users agree and accept that confidentiality of information posted on such features has been waived by the Users of such features themselves.

**Data Security:** No data broadcast over the internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. So while we strive to protect such information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

**Policy Update:** DeColore.net reserves the rights to update & modify the privacy policy time to time whenever required, it is user’s responsibility to check the policy detail & keep informed.

**Affiliate Disclosure:** We often produce content where we are affiliate to the product and services we write about and earn commission if you make a purchase any product or service through our link. DeColore.net take no responsibility of any fault or non delivery of product or services you purchase through our like. You are liable to take your own decision before you make the purchase.
